<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Diego Calanzone</title><link>https://halixness.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Diego Calanzone</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Diego Calanzone 2021</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 13:00:01 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://halixness.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The consequences of social media</title><link>https://halixness.github.io/posts/consequences-social/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 13:00:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://halixness.github.io/posts/consequences-social/</guid><description>Introduction This article derives from an essay I wrote for my dream university. Beyond the academic purpose, this article is motivated by a deep interest in studying the dynamics of society and its most influential factors. You can check the references for each fact for further research, or to assess the validity of my statements, which reflect my vision on the topic.
Credits to @robert_rednine from unsplash.com
The popularity of social media have steadily grown for the last 15 years: 2.</description></item><item><title>Exercise and longevity (Gremeaux et al. 2012)</title><link>https://halixness.github.io/what-im-reading/exercise-longevity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2021 13:35:01 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://halixness.github.io/what-im-reading/exercise-longevity/</guid><description>This paper was written by the Cardiovascular Prevention and Rehabilitation Center (Centre ÉPIC) in Montreal, Canada, in collaboration with CHU Poitiers, CHU Dijon and the University of Poitiers in France.
Longevity, the ability to reach an age above average, is influenced by intrinsic (genetic) and extrinsic factors (lifestyle, nutrition, mental and physical wellbeing). In this paper, the authors suggest there is a correlation between exercise and reduction in risks for cardiovascular diseases, various forms of cancer and decaying in muscles and the skeleton; moreover, such correlation may be proportional to the exercise volume (duration x intensity).</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://halixness.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:42:36 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://halixness.github.io/about/</guid><description>"A mind is a parachute, it doesn't work if you don't open it". E-mail Resumé Linkedin Github I graduated in Computer Science in 2021 at the University of Parma, Italy. I am junior software engineer and my current focus is Deep Learning: Self Supervised Learning Multi-modal learning Language models Reinforcement Learning I am also interested in life-long investing, longevity, sociology and visual arts.</description></item></channel></rss>