<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>page on Diego Calanzone</title><link>https://halixness.github.io/categories/page/</link><description>Recent content in page on Diego Calanzone</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>© Diego Calanzone 2021</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:42:36 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://halixness.github.io/categories/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://halixness.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 22:42:36 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://halixness.github.io/about/</guid><description>"A mind is a parachute, it doesn't work if you don't open it". E-mail Resumé Linkedin Github I graduated in Computer Science in 2021 at the University of Parma, Italy. I am junior software engineer and my current focus is Deep Learning: Self Supervised Learning Multi-modal learning Language models Reinforcement Learning I am also interested in life-long investing, longevity, sociology and visual arts.</description></item><item><title>deepSWE: video prediction applied on shallow water equations.</title><link>https://halixness.github.io/projects/deep-learning/deepswe/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halixness.github.io/projects/deep-learning/deepswe/</guid><description>TL;DR: you can read the paper here (Italian) and check the repository.
Between late 2020 and summer 2021, I had the pleasure to work with Prof. Alessandro Dal Palú and the HyLab research team at the University of Parma. The subject for this thesis project is Shallow Water Equations and methods in deep learning to compute them with cost and time efficiency.
My proposal was an initial approach to video prediction models: the flooding scenario is discretized into a 2D grid with variable resolution.</description></item><item><title>Learning Transferable Visual Models From Natural Language Supervision</title><link>https://halixness.github.io/projects/deep-learning/clip-seminar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halixness.github.io/projects/deep-learning/clip-seminar/</guid><description>TL;DR: you can find the repository here.
In october 2021 I joined the seminar &amp;ldquo;Learning with Limited labeled data&amp;rdquo; at the University of Tuebingen. I decided to study and present the model &amp;ldquo;CLIP&amp;rdquo; and correlated: DALL-E, Big Sleep, CLIP GLaSS.
Briefly, in this paper a novel approach for natural language vision is proposed: in order to link text with images, captions and photos are encoded as vectors in the same embedding space, with contrastive learning the model learns to best match these vectors.</description></item><item><title>The EDGY - a software engineering project</title><link>https://halixness.github.io/projects/swe/comp-2913-the-edgy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://halixness.github.io/projects/swe/comp-2913-the-edgy/</guid><description>TL;DR: you can find the repository here. For the demo, click here.
This repository contains a complete platform for an ideal sports center, developed with an AGILE-Scrum based approach in team. You can access the demo here (heroku hosted).
This software has been developed in team at the University of Leeds for the COMP2913 module. The team:
Diego Calanzone Sam Barnes Joe Jeffcock Artyom Tunelis Georgy Gunkin</description></item></channel></rss>